

### CONTACT

- portfolio: <a href="https://magdalenaszpita">https://magdalenaszpita</a>
  <a href="https://magdalenaszpita">lna-portfolio.netlify.app/</a>
- magdalenaszpitalna@gmail.com
- in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/magdalena-szpitalna-/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/magdalena-szpitalna-/</a>
- https://github.com/MadzikResist
- 665 575 835

### **EDUCATION**

Information and Communications Technology Poznań University of Technology 2019-2023

#### SKILLS

HTML5 PostgreSQL

CSS MongoDB

JavaScript

React

React Native

Node JS

Express.JS

# MAGDALENA SZPITALNA

### **ABOUT ME**

I am 23 years old and I am an IT enthusiast ready for new challenges in the field of programming.

My experience with various technologies allows me to combine acquired knowledge with a creative approach to projects.

I possess flexibility in problem-solving and the ability to quickly grasp new concepts. I am ready to join a team where I can effectively utilize my skills and collaboratively create innovative solutions.

### **EXPERIENCE**

CO-FOUNDER

08.2023 - Present

**MEETZ** 

Creating a mobile application for making friends.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

12.2022-12.2023

**CODEALLY** 

Developing software for a platform that hires programmers.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

06.2022-09.2022

**INTERNSHIP** 

Backend and Frontend website development

## **LANGUAGES**

**ENGLISH** B2